Help

Privacy policy

Last update: December 9, 2022,

We are very committed to providing you with a fun, entertaining, and safe experience when visiting the goSupermodel website.  
In order to do that, we collect, monitor and store various kinds of information about our users and visitors and their online behaviour. This Privacy Policy describes how we use such information.  
We constantly offer new features and content to our users, and therefore we reserve the right to, from time to time and at our own sole discretion, change this Privacy Policy to fit with our needs. Please make sure that you regularly return here to make sure you are aware of our current practices. We always treat all collected personal information in accordance with the Privacy Policy in effect at the time the information is collected. The date of effect of this Privacy Policy is stated at the top.

1\. What Information We Collect
===============================

Generally speaking we collect two types of information. The first type is information that you actively submit, whereas the second type is information that is automatically collected as part of your visit on goSupermodel.

Text
----

We collect and store all text that you write on goSupermodel. This includes content from the profile pages, the forum, the chat, private messages, messages to all, clubs, etc.  
All text you write on goSupermodel is available for our trained, paid staff, to investigate in cases of reports by other users or flags for suspicious behaviour by our automated safety systems

Pictures
--------

All pictures that you upload to or generate on goSupermodel are stored. We screen all pictures to decide if they are allowed on the website. This is part of our extensive safety system and ensures that inappropriate pictures are not published. Rejected pictures are also stored!

Date of Birth
-------------

You can enter your date of birth on the Settings page, in which case we will show your star sign on your profile page. However, this is not mandatory and is entirely up to you. Note the actual date of birth will not be visible to other users.

E-mail
------

We store any e-mail address you may register on goSupermodel.

Session Data
------------

We collect various so-called session data which is basically information on when you log in and out of goSupermodel and what actions you make while logged in.

Cookies
-------

A cookie is a small information (ID) file which we place permanently on your computer. The cookie makes goSupermodel recognizable on your computer and is used to improve user-friendliness.  
Another type is session cookies. They are saved temporarily on your computer when you visit goSupermodel, but disappear when you close down the page. It means that they are not saved permanently on your hard disk.  
If you would like to know when your computer receives a cookie, you can set your browser to inform you when it receives a cookie. This way, you may select or reject a cookie. You can also set your computer to reject all cookies entirely.  
You need to be aware, however, that any changes in your browser may prevent goSupermodel from working properly!

IP Address
----------

Even if you have decided to reject cookies, we are able to record your visit via your IP address. An IP address is a numeric value, which automatically identifies your computer when you are on the Internet.

Computer Operating System
-------------------------

We collect information on what computer operating system you use (e.g., Windows XP or Mac OS) so that we may better help you if you have technical problems related to that when you visit goSupermodel.

Web Browser
-----------

We also collect information on what web browser you use (e.g., Firefox, Internet Explorer) so that we may better help you if you have technical problems related to that when you visit goSupermodel.

Other Information
-----------------

For some of our activities we may ask you to provide us with additional information. For instance, if you have won a competition and we need to send you the prize in the post, we may ask for your home address and full name. From time to time, we also use the information you provide about yourself or others as well as conduct member surveys in order to improve our services. However, we do not keep any such personal information we obtain beyond the time it is needed.

2\. How We Use collected Information
====================================

We are very committed to maintaining high safety standards so that you can feel safe when using goSupermodel. Therefore, the primary use for the information we collect from our users is to make sure that everybody is respecting the rules and each other. Collected Information is fed to our automatic and manual safety tools so that we can easily look out for inappropriate behaviour (e.g. bullying, vulgar language, etc.). If we discover that someone is violating the goSupermodel rules or our [Terms & Conditions](http://gosupermodel.com/support/page.jsp?id=124), we will take the appropriate action against that user (e.g. warning, time-out, ban from the website, etc.).

We sometimes use the information that we collect from you and other users to generate various statistics that allow us to improve the design and content of our website, to personalize your experience on goSupermodel, and to make new features and games. We also may use this information as a collective to analyze site usage - for instance how many visitors we have and how they surf on our homepage. We can check which homepages visitors come from, and we can see when, how long and how they use the information on our homepage. This again is sometimes used to target our advertising on goSupermodel.

We use your e-mail addresses to send out our news letters to users that have requested to receive them. You can select this under settings and you can always go back and de-select it again (note that you also opt out by clicking on the opt out link in a news letter).  
Also, if you should forget your goSupermodel password we can send it to your e-mail.

3\. Distribution of Information to Third-Parties
================================================

We do not distribute any personal information collected form you to any third-parties. We may, however, disclose collective information such as usage statistics to third-parties (e.g. advertising agencies or content providers) as part of our marketing strategies or to improve the website.

We will disclose information we maintain when required to do so by law, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena. We also may disclose such information to a law enforcement agency or other public agency if we find content or materials that seem suspicious or is in violation with the law and if we feel that such disclosure may prevent the instigation of a crime.

Finally, we may disclose information to a potential purchaser of goSupermodel acquiring all or most of the assets relating to goSupermodel, to the extent permitted by law.

4\. Security
============

We have all the appropriate physical, electronic, and administrative procedures in place to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the information we collect online.

5\. Financial Information
=========================

If you purchase VIP, goMoney or Diamonds via the options presented on our website, we store the amounts of what bought, what payment method you used, and the fact that you have bought one of these things. We do not collect any further information on you - except when you buy via SMS in which case we will collect and store your phone number (see above for further details). Additional information (such as credit card details) may be required on goMoney, Diamond or VIP purchases that are not handled via SMS. Such information is not collected or stored by us but is handled by our payment solution partners and it will never be used for any other purposes than processing the purchase. Please read their privacy policies for further details on what information is collected.

6\. Your Rights of Review
=========================

Should you request to have information that we have collected on you deleted, or request that we no longer collect or maintain such information, then please send a letter or postcard to us at the mailing address provided below. Please be sure to include your model name, email address and a telephone number where we can reach you. To protect our users' privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting you access to any information.

Att.: goSupermodel Community Manager  
watAgame Aps  
Kigkurren 8C, 1. sal  
2300 Copenhagen S  
Denmark

Please note that your use of goSupermodel signifies your acceptance of our collecting of information. If you no longer wish that we collect information on you, you must immediately stop using goSupermodel.

7\. Note to Parents
===================

We encourage you to involve yourself in your child's online experiences. This may ensure that the proper practises are learned from the start and may help your child understand the pitfalls of the Internet. We do a lot to educate our users on how to handle personal information, but your guidance and involvement are also essential to help ensure that your child has a safe and rewarding online experience.

8\. Contact Us
==============

If you have any questions or comments concerning your visit to goSupermodel, please write to the Community Manager at: [gosupermodel@watagame.com](mailto:gosupermodel@watagame.com)

Back

About
-----

Contact
-------

Help
----

Membership
----------

Social media
------------

goSupermodel™ Momio ApS. © 2023. All rights reserved.
